London, United Kingdom brodskiedward@gmail.com

Edward Brodski Software Engineer/Project Manager

linkedin.com/in/edward-brodski Portfolio: edwardbrodski.com

Passionate Software Engineer and Project Manager with 7+ years of programming experience, 2+ years of work experience and a Master's degree in Computer Science.

Areas of expertise: Python Scripting, Frontend, Workflow design and Task Management.

EXPERIENCE

Project Manager Jun 2022 — Sep 2022 NDB

Worked Remotely

- Managed the design team, ensuring correct workflows and descriptions ready for implementation.
- · Handled administration for the company's community resources as well as creating specialized Discord and Telegram bots for marketing and community management purposes.
- Ensured task completion for the software team, maintained SCRUM boards.
- Evaluated completed work, testing for User Interaction, Security and performance.

Software Engineer Aug 2020 — Feb 2022

OptimumSoftware Worked Remotely

- Developed the UI for the business facing component of "Subscribr" with React.
- Contributed to the internal GraphQL API systems.
- Worked with designers to refine the quality and presentation of information across all relevant websites.

PROJECTS

Context-Free-Grammar Equivalence Research Project, Python, NumPy, Pandas

Jun 2021 — May 2022

- Produced the first Open Source implementation of a state-of-the-art algorithm for evaluating grammar equivalence.
- Developed testing methods for the evaluation of different approaches presented by other works as well as my own.

Personalized Finance Assistant, Python, Pandas, Tk

Aug 2022 — Jul 2023

- Developed infrastructure to ingest and unify different transaction streams into a single database.
- Implemented an integrated labelling and tagging system.
- Designed and produced a GUI application for the classification and analysis of data providing an integrated view of graphics and

Intelligent Early Wildfire Detection, Python, Pandas, PyTorch

Sep 2022 — Jun 2023

- Researched Wildfire smoke patterns and developed as system for automatically generating fire patterns for AI training and testing.
- Carried out Data Analysis and validation for the generated datasets
- Trained a final model which reached an accuracy of 96.72%

Snake Evolution, Python

Mar 2019 — Oct 2020

- Designed a flexible grid based ecosystem with a graphical output.
- Developed a gene system and offspring gene randomization for the snakes.
- Added data analyzation systems such as live graphs and decision visualizations.

3D Modelling and Design, Fusion 360

- I have designed and modelled a magnitude of different hardware projects.
- · Worked closely with 3D Printing technology gaining experience in designing for and working with 3D Printers.
- Items such as Keyboards, Desk Fans, Organizers, and light fixtures.
- You can see some of my projects here https://www.printables.com/@Edward/models

EDUCATION

MSci Computer Science, Queen Mary University of London: First-Class

Sep 2019 — Jul 2023

Senior School, Millfield, Computer Science $-A^*$, Further Mathematics -A, Mathematics $-A^*$, Physics -A

Sep 2017 — Jun 2019

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python, TypeScript, JavaScript, C++, Java **Programming Languages**

Technologies NodeJS, React, React-Native, HTML, CSS, NumPy, Pandas, PyTorch, REST, GraphQL, AWS

Tools Git, GitHub, Linux, Docker, Fusion 360, Jira, Figma, ClickUp

Additional Courses MHFA(Mental Health First Aid) England Completed in Jan 2023